Alexander, Gabriel Arbitration Files 5133
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Gabriel Alexander Arbitration Files
1947-1974
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Alexander, Gabriel
5133
46 cubic feet
46 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3118562
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 01, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 07, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Independent arbitrator, attorney and adjunct professor of labor arbitration.
Gabriel N. Alexander holds a JD from the University of Michigan (1933). He was a partner in the law firm of Alexander and Alexander (1933-1948) after which he served as hearing officer for the Automotive Section of the U.S. War Labor Board (1945-1946).
Alexander was impartial umpire for General Motors Corporation vs. the International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW) (1948-1954), Bower Roller Bearing Company vs. UAW (1956- 1959), and Chrysler Corporation vs. UAW; impartial chairman for Jones & Laughlin Steel Company vs. United Steelworkers of America (USWA) (1960-1961), Major League Baseball Clubs vs. Players Association (1972-1974), Clark Equipment Company vs. UAW (1966-1971), and Armco Incorporated vs. USWA; arbitrator for Bethlehem Steel Company vs. USWA (1954-1955); permanent arbitrator for International Harvester vs. UAW (1964-1976), and John Deere Horicon Works vs. UAW (1968-1971). Additionally, Alexander served as a member on arbitration panels for General Motors Corporation vs. United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, Greyhound Bus Lines vs. Amalgamated Transit Union, American Airlines Corporation vs. Airline Stewards and Stewardesses Association, and U.S. Steel Corporation vs. Salaried Employees Association.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5602: Gabriel Alexander Additional Arbitration Files 5678: Gabriel Alexander Additional Arbitration Files 5789: Gabriel Alexander Additional Arbitration Files /4107: Kheel Center Additional Cataloging Project Work notes 6435: Gabriel Alexander Collections
Arbitration, Industrial--United States--Sources.; Alexander, Gabriel N.
3118562
- Aeroquip Corporation, - Armco Steel Corporation. (Box 1)
  - Aeroquip Corporation - Local 475, United Auto Workers, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Albion Malleable Iron Company - United Auto Workers Local 474, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Algonac Foundry Company - United Auto Workers, Local 1182, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen-Bradley Company - United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America Local 1111, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corporation - United Steelworkers of America Local 2242, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes photographs
  - Allen-Bradley - Wireman and Special Assembler, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Allied Paper Corporation, Bryant Mill - Local 426, United Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Allied Paper Corporation (King Division) - Local 649, United Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Allied Paper Corporation (Monach Division) - Local 667, United Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Allis-Chalmers Manufacturing Company - Local 555, United Plant Guard Workers of America, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - American Agricultural Chemicals Company - Local 12093, United Mine Workers of America, District 50 (Ferdinand Chowanski), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    February 6, 1958
  - American Bakeries - International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 51, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - American Bakeries Company - Firemen and Oilers Union Local 32, 1954-1962 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - American Coupling Corporation - Local 949, International Union of Electrical Workers, 1961-1965 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - American International Aluminum Corporation - International Molders and Allied Workers Union, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - American-Marietta - United Mine Workers District 50, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Applegate Chevrolet - United Auto Workers, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Union Wire Rope-Armco Steel Corporation - United Steelworkers of America 1011, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Armco Steel Corporation - United Steelworkers, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Armco Steel Corporation - United Steelworkers, 1958-1966 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Armco Steel Corporation - Bower Roller Bearing Co.. (Box 2)
  - Armco Steel Corporation - United Steelworkers, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Automatic Music, Incorporated - International Union of Electrical Workers Local 981, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    December 1961
  - Automatic Music, Incorporated - Local 981, International Union of Electrical Workers, 1957-1960 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bell Bakeries - Detroit Bakery Workers Local 326, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Bliss and Laughlin Industries, Incorporated Grievance 1 - United Steelworkers of America, 1954-1966 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers, and Helpers, 1958-1961 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - United Steel Workers Local 2499, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - United Steelworkers Local 2598, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    January 20, 1955
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - United Steelworkers Local 2598, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - United Steelworkers of America, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    February 23, 1955
  - Bethlehem Steel Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 2599, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    March 22, 1955
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - United Steelworkers of America, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    March 31, 1955
  - Bethlehem Steel Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 2604, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    May 24, 1955
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - United Steelworkers of America Local 2604, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - United Steelworkers of America Local 2604, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    May 25, 1955
  - Bethlehem Steel Company - Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - The Borden Company (Saginaw) - United Dairy and Bakery Workers Local 87, 1955-1959 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Bower Roller Bearing Division of Federal-Mogul Bower Bearings, Incorporated - United Auto Workers of America Local 681, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bower Roller Bearing - 7 Discharges, 1955-1957 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Bower Roller Bearings - United Auto Workers Local 681, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Bower Roller Bearings and Local 114, United Plant Guard Workers of America, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Bower Roller Bearings - Loudre-Bowman Discharges, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Bower Roller Bearing - Grievance 2092, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Bower Roller Bearing - Local 681, United Auto Workers of America, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Bower Roller Bearing - Local 681, United Auto Workers of America, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681 Ump. Dec. 19, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Bower Roller Bearing - U.A.W., 1956 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Bower-, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Bower Roller Bearing- U.A.W. AFL-CIO, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Bower Roller Bearing Co. - L.C. Clark Hauling Co.. (Box 3)
  - Bower Roller Bearing and Local 681, UAW, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1962 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1966 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1966 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1966 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1966 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1966 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1966 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1966 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1966 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1966 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1966 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1966 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Bower Roller Bearing -and- Local 681, U.A.W., 1967 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Bowman Sealrich Dairy Co. (Saginaw) -and- Local 87 United Dairy and Bakery Workers, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Wm. J. Burns International Detective Agency -and- Amalgamated Local No. 168, UPGWA, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Wm. J. Burns International Detective Agency (Detroit) -and- Local 114, U.P.G.W.A., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Cadillac Marine and Boat Co. -and- I.A.M. Lodge 1757, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - S. H. Camp and Co. (Jackson, Mich.) -and- I.L.G.W.U., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Celanese Corp. of America Narrows, Va. -and- Local 153 United Construction Workers, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Celanese Fibers Company -and- District 50 U.M.W.A., Local 15153, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - L.C. Clark, Hauling - Teamsters Local 299, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Clark Equipment Com.. (Box 4)
  - Clark Equipment Co. -and- UAW, Local 468, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 62-65, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 77-65, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 58-65, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 102-65, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 96-65, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 128-65, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 82-65, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 117-65, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 139-65, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 137-65, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 106-65, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 145-65, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 154-65, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 188-65, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 177-65, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 315-65, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 276-65, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 272-65, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 263-65, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 2-66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 40-66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 1-66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 37-66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 37-66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 207-66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 307-66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 530-66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 386-66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 431-66, 447-66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 434-66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 536-66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 1-67, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 35-67, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 117-66, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 606-66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 639-66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr 892-66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 775-66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 805-66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 953-66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 486 Gr. 803-66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 486 Gr. 859-66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 486 Gr. 878-66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 486 Gr. 902-66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 486 Gr. 678-66, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 120-67, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 74-67, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 486 Gr. 9-67, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 37-67, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 41-67, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW, Local 468 Gr. 70-67, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Clark Equipment Co. - Dearborn Beer Distributing. (Box 5)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 31-67, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 184-67, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Local 468 Gr. 190-67, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 254-67, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 201-67, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 202-67, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 214-67, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 264-67, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 335-8, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 385-8, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 108-9, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 125-9, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 285-8, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 253-9, 260-9, 261-9, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 292-9 and 293-9, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 416-9, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 445-9, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 382-9, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 489-9, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 504-9, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 526-9, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 467-9 and 469-9, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 501-9, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 503-9, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 386-7, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 462-9, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 603-9, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 698-9, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 495-9, 505-9, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 497-9, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 69-181, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Clark Equipment Company -and- UAW Gr. 69-183, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Cliffs Dow Chemical Co. -and- UMWA, District 30 Gr., 1966 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Columbus Auto Parts Co. -and- Buckeye Lodge 55, I.A.M., 1961 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Construction Workers Fund, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Continental Can Co. Inc. -and- Dist. 50. UMWA, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Cornell Paperboard Prod. Co. -and- Local 200 International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill Workers, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Crucible Steel Co. -and- U.S.W.A. Gr. 1037, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Dayton Power and Light Company -and- Local 175 Utility Workers of America, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Dayton Power and Light Co. -and- Utility Workers of America, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - The Dayton Tire and Rubber Co. -and- Local 178 URCLPWA, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Dearborn Beer Distributors -and- Local 38 International Union, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Deere and Company. (Box 6)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr. 68-11, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - John Deere Horicon Works Gr. 575-576 -and- Local 873 and 433 International Molders, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr. 67-819, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr. 68-168, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr. 68-1077, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr. 68-169, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr. 66-43, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr. 67-176, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr. 67-247, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr. 68-91, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr. 68-1158, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr. 65-1034, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr. 68-178, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr. 68-332, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr. 65-1216, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr. 65-1423, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr. 6, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr., 1965-1969 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr. 68-719, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr. 64955, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Deere and Company -and- United Auto and Aerospace Workers of America Gr. 6853-15, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 22)